let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question:
        " Design a problem that involves calculating the interior angles of a regular hexagon.",
      answer: "A. 120°",
      options: ["A. 120°", "B. 135°", "C. 140°", "D. 150°"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " Create a scenario where students have to determine the number of sides in a polygon based on the given interior angle measurement.",
      answer: " C. 8",
      options: [
        "A. 6",
        "B. 7",
        "C. 8",
        "D. 9",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 3,
      question:
        " Invent a problem that requires calculating the exterior angles of a regular pentagon.",
      answer: "B. 72°",
      options: [
        "A. 60°",
        "B. 72°",
        "C. 90°",
        "D. 108°",
      ],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Develop a question that challenges students to identify the type of polygon based on the given angle measures.",
      answer: "C. Pentagon",
      options: ["A. Triangle", "B. Quadrilateral", "C. Pentagon", "D. Hexagon"],
    },
  
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: " Create a problem where students need to calculate the missing angle in a parallelogram.",
      answer: "B. 100°",
      options: [
        "A. 90°",
        "B. 100°",
        "C. 110°",
        "D. 120°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Construct a scenario where students have to determine the measure of each interior angle in a regular octagon.",
      answer: "B. 135°",
      options: [
        "A. 120°",
        "B. 135°",
        "C. 140°",
        "D. 150°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 7,
      question: " Invent a problem that involves calculating the total number of degrees in the exterior angles of a convex polygon.",
      answer: "A. 360°",
      options: [
        "A. 360°",
        "B. 450°",
        "C. 540°",
        "D. 720°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 8,
      question: " Design a problem where students need to determine the type of triangle based on side length information.",
      answer: "C. Scalene",
      options: [
        "A. Equilateral",
        "B. Isosceles°",
        "C. Scalene",
        "D. Right-angled",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "  Create a scenario where students have to calculate the measure of each interior angle in a convex heptagon.",
      answer: "D. 135°",
      options: [
        "A. 120°",
        "B. 125°",
        "C. 130°",
        "D. 135°",
      ],
    },

    {
      numb: 10,
      question: " Invent a problem that requires students to determine the type of quadrilateral based on the given angle measures.",
      answer: "A. Parallelogram",
      options: [
        "A. Parallelogram",
        "B. Rhombus",
        "C. Rectangle",
        "D. Trapezoid",
      ],
    },
  ];
  